[
    {
      "quiz_id": 1,
      "scientific_name": "Allamanda cathartica",
      "question": "Allamanda Cathartica plant is native to?",
      "options": "Brazil, Argentina, Puerto Rico, India",
      "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 2,
      "scientific_name": "Allamanda cathartica",
      "question": "Allamanda Cathartica max height is?",
      "options": "10 feet, 12 feet, 17 feet, 20 feet",
      "answer": "20 feet"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 3,
      "scientific_name": "Roystonea regia",
      "question": "Royal palm plant is native to?",
      "options": "Brazil, Mexico, Japan, Canada",
      "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 4,
      "scientific_name": "Roystonea regia",
      "question": "Royal palm was first discovered by?",
      "options": "William Bartram, Albert Einstein, Jeff Bezos,Orator F. Cook",
      "answer": "Orator F. Cook"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 5,
      "scientific_name": "Bismarckia nobilis",
      "question": "Bismarckia nobilis plant is native to?",
      "options": "Sudan, Nigeria, Madagascar, France",
      "answer": "Madagascar"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 6,
      "scientific_name": "Bismarckia nobilis",
      "question": "When should Bismarackia nobilis be pruned?",
      "options": "Summer, Fall, Anytime of the year, January-March",
      "answer": "Anytime of the year"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 7,
      "scientific_name": "Pterocarpus Indicus ",
      "question": "How tall does Pterocarpus Indicus grow?",
      "options": "30-40m, 40-50m, 100-120m, 10-20m",
      "answer": "30-40m"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 8,
      "scientific_name": "Pterocarpus Indicus",
      "question": "In which country do you require a permit to cut Pterocarpus Indicus?",
      "options": "Canada, Japan, Phillipines, Indonesia",
      "answer": "Phillipines"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 9,
      "scientific_name": "Millettia pinnata",
      "question": "Millettia pinnata has a light brown bark",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 10,
      "scientific_name": "Millettia pinnata",
      "question": "Millettia pinnata can grow at high altitudes",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 11,
      "scientific_name": "Saraca Asoca",
      "question": "Saraca Asoca was named after which famous king?",
      "options": "King Prithviraj Chauhan, King Ashoka, Emperor Humayun, Alexander the Great",
      "answer": "King Ashoka"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 12,
      "scientific_name": "Saraca Asoca",
      "question": "The flower of Saraca Asoca is the state flower of which Indian state?",
      "options": "Jharkhand, Uttar pradesh, Odisha, Gujarat",
      "answer": "Odisha"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 13,
      "scientific_name": "Ficus elastica",
      "question": "The Ficus elastica has \"fake fruits\"",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 14,
      "scientific_name": "Ficus elastica",
      "question": "Ficus Elastica has a high tolerance to droughts",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 15,
      "scientific_name": "Bridelia Retusa",
      "question": "Bridelia retusa has a slow growth rate",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 16,
      "scientific_name": "Bridelia Retusa",
      "question": "Bridelia retusas bark can be used as poison",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 17,
      "scientific_name": "Spathodea campanulata",
      "question": "Spathodea campanulata may grow to 120ft",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 18,
      "scientific_name": "Spathodea campanulata",
      "question": "Spathodea campanulata is an evergreen tree",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 19,
      "scientific_name": "Alstonia Scholaris",
      "question": "Alstonia Scholaris is a toxic plant",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 20,
      "scientific_name": "Alstonia Scholaris",
      "question": "In some places, the trunk of Alstonia Scholaris is three sided",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 21,
      "scientific_name": "Nux vomica",
      "question": "Which of the following is not treated with Nux vomica",
      "options": "Constipation, Migraine, Anxiety, Depression",
      "answer": "Depression"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 22,
      "scientific_name": "Nux vomica",
      "question": "Even though it has medicinal properties, it is also used as rat poison",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 23,
      "scientific_name": "Indian willow",
      "question": "Indian willows flower is used in preparing a dish",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 24,
      "scientific_name": "Indian willow",
      "question": "Indian willows bark is used to treat diarrhea",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 25,
      "scientific_name": "Syzygium cumini",
      "question": "Syzygium cuminis fruit looks like a blueberry",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 26,
      "scientific_name": "Syzygium cumini",
      "question": "Syzygium cumini is a cheap alternative to build furniture",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 27,
      "scientific_name": "Artocarpus heterophyllus",
      "question": "Artocarpus heterophylluss chips are a popular snack",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 28,
      "scientific_name": "Artocarpus heterophyllus",
      "question": "Artocarpus heterophyllus is the state fruit of?",
      "options": "Gujarat, Karnataka, West Bengal, Kerala",
      "answer": "Kerala"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 29,
      "scientific_name": "Callistemon viminalis",
      "question": "Callistemon viminaliss flower is",
      "options": "Bright green, bright orange, dull yellow, bright red",
      "answer": "bright red"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 30,
      "scientific_name": "Callistemon viminalis",
      "question": "Callistemon viminalis resembles which cleaning utensil?",
      "options": "Bottlebrush, Scrub",
      "answer": "Bottlebrush"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 31,
      "scientific_name": "Terminalia catappa",
      "question": "Terminalia catappas leaves are used by?",
      "options": "Fish breeders, Bird breeders, Apiarists, Dentists",
      "answer": "Fish breeders"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 32,
      "scientific_name": "Terminalia catappa",
      "question": "Terminalia catappas fruit has how many seeds?",
      "options": "Two, One, More than 100, Around 10-20",
      "answer": "One"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 33,
      "scientific_name": "Mangifera indica",
      "question": "Mangifera indicas fruit is shaped like a?",
      "options": "Kidney, Ear, brain, eye",
      "answer": "Kidney"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 34,
      "scientific_name": "Mangifera indica",
      "question": "Mangifera indicas fruits juice is bitter",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 35,
      "scientific_name": "Filicium decipiens",
      "question": "Filicium decipienss mature fruit is",
      "options": "Purple, Green, Red, Orange",
      "answer": "Purple"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 36,
      "scientific_name": "Filicium decipiens",
      "question": "Filicium refers to the roots of the tree",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 37,
      "scientific_name": "Millingtonia hortensis",
      "question": "Millingtonia hortensis can be used as a substitute for true cork",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 38,
      "scientific_name": "Millingtonia hortensis",
      "question": "Millingtonia hortensiss flowers are ornamental",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 39,
      "scientific_name": "Cuban pink trumpet",
      "question": "Cuban pink trumpets flowers are",
      "options": "Pink, Purple, Bright red, Violet",
      "answer": "Pink"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 40,
      "scientific_name": "Cuban pink trumpet",
      "question": "Cuban pink trumpets flowers are used in making",
      "options": "Coffee, tea, juice, medicinal drink",
      "answer": "tea"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 41,
      "scientific_name": "Grewia tilifolia",
      "question": "What part of Grewia tilifolia is used to treat fractures?",
      "options": "Bark, Flower, Stem, Branch",
      "answer": "Bark"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 42,
      "scientific_name": "Grewia tilifolia",
      "question": "Grewia tilifolias wood is used for tool handles",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 43,
      "scientific_name": "Copper Pod",
      "question": "Copper Pods timber is used for cabinet work",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 44,
      "scientific_name": "Copper Pod",
      "question": "Copper Pod is an ornamental tree in many parts of the world",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 45,
      "scientific_name": "Yellow cheesewood",
      "question": "What part Yellow cheesewood is used to treat animal bites",
      "options": "Leaf, roots, bark, sap",
      "answer": "bark"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 46,
      "scientific_name": "Yellow cheesewood",
      "question": "Yellow cheesewoods fruits are ",
      "options": "Sweet, sour, bitter, flavorless",
      "answer": "Bitter"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 47,
      "scientific_name": "Ceylon satinwood",
      "question": "Which present day country was previously called Ceylon?",
      "options": "Singapore, Malaysia, Sri Lanka, Indonesia",
      "answer": "Sri Lanka"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 48,
      "scientific_name": "Ceylon satinwood",
      "question": "Dried leaves of Ceylon satinwood speeds up healing process",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 49,
      "scientific_name": "Royal poinciana",
      "question": "Royal poinciana is also called flame of the forest",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 50,
      "scientific_name": "Royal poinciana",
      "question": "Can the Royal poinciana be used to give shade?",
      "options": "Yes, No",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 51,
      "scientific_name": "Kindal",
      "question": "Kindals timber is strong enough to be used to build ships",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 52,
      "scientific_name": "Kindal",
      "question": "What makes this tree so colorful?",
      "options": "Fruit, Flowers",
      "answer": "Fruit"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 53,
      "scientific_name": "Notched leaf soap nut",
      "question": "What part of Notched leaf soap nut has medicinal properties",
      "options": "Fruit, Flowers,leaf,bark",
      "answer": "Fruit"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 54,
      "scientific_name": "Notched leaf soap nut",
      "question": "Notched leaf soap nuts fruit can help cure migraines",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 55,
      "scientific_name": "Thespesia populnea",
      "question": "Thespesia populneas wood is used in the making of which instrument?",
      "options": "Hourglass drum, Guitar, Maracas, Drum sticks",
      "answer": "Hourglass drum"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 56,
      "scientific_name": "Thespesia populnea",
      "question": "Flower of Thespesia populnea played a part in which countrys independence movement?",
      "options": "Singapore, Malaysia, Sri Lanka, Indonesia",
      "answer": "Sri Lanka"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 57,
      "scientific_name": "Spanish cherry",
      "question": "Spanish cherry is used in Ayurvedic treatment",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 58,
      "scientific_name": "Spanish cherry",
      "question": "Spanish cherrys flowers are used to make green tea in",
      "options": "Singapore, Malaysia, Sri Lanka, Thailand",
      "answer": "Thailand"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 59,
      "scientific_name": "Azadirachta indica",
      "question": "Azadirachta indicas leaves can be placed in cupboards to prevent insects from eating clothes",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 60,
      "scientific_name": "Azadirachta indica",
      "question": "Azadirachta indica can be used as fertilizer",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 61,
      "scientific_name": "Gold shower",
      "question": "Gold shower is the national tree for which country?",
      "options": "Singapore, Malaysia, Sri Lanka, Thailand",
      "answer": "Thailand"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 62,
      "scientific_name": "Gold shower",
      "question": "Gold showers yellow flowers symbolize Japanese royalty",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 63,
      "scientific_name": "Ben teak",
      "question": "Does the Ben teaks bark peel off in strips or fall off in chunks",
      "options": "Strips, Chunks",
      "answer": "Strips"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 64,
      "scientific_name": "Ben teak",
      "question": "Ben teaks scientific name is named after a naturalist from which country?",
      "options": "Iceland, Finland, Sweden, Switzerland",
      "answer": "Sweden"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 65,
      "scientific_name": "Albizia lebbeck",
      "question": "Ancient kings wore garlands from the Albizia lebbecks flowers to celebrate what?",
      "options": "Prosperity, Peace, Victory, Greenery",
      "answer": "Victory"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 66,
      "scientific_name": "Albizia lebbeck",
      "question": "Albizia lebbecks bark can be used to treat inflamation",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 67,
      "scientific_name": "Pink Lapacho",
      "question": "Pink Lapacho is the national tree of ",
      "options": "Paraguay, Uruguay, Argentina, Somalia",
      "answer": "Paraguay"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 68,
      "scientific_name": "Pink Lapacho",
      "question": "Pink Lapacho can be used to cure smokers cough",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 69,
      "scientific_name": "Indian cherry",
      "question": "Indian cherrys fruit usually ripens from",
      "options": "November to January, August to October",
      "answer": "August to October"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 70,
      "scientific_name": "Indian cherry",
      "question": "Indian cherry is a small tree",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 71,
      "scientific_name": "Costus spectabilis",
      "question": "Costus spectabiliss flower was used in which celebritys wedding",
      "options": "Meghan markle, Amy Adams, Margot Robbie, Dakota Johnson",
      "answer": "Meghan markle"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 72,
      "scientific_name": "Costus spectabilis",
      "question": "Costus spectabilis is mostly found in which continent",
      "options": "Asia, Europe, South America, Africa",
      "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 73,
      "scientific_name": "Marking nut tree",
      "question": "Marking nut tree is called marking nut tree because it was used to mark trees",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 74,
      "scientific_name": "Marking nut tree",
      "question": "Marking nut trees fruit is similar to which fruit",
      "options": "Cashew, Almond, Plum, Papaya",
      "answer": "Cashew"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 75,
      "scientific_name": "Dinner plate tree",
      "question": "Dinner plate trees name comes from the fact that its leaves look like dinner plates",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 76,
      "scientific_name": "Dinner plate tree",
      "question": "The wood of the Dinner plate tree is not strong but it is durable",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 77,
      "scientific_name": "Blue Marble tree",
      "question": "The cleaned pits of the Blue marble trees fruit are used to make rudraksh malas",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 78,
      "scientific_name": "Blue Marble tree",
      "question": "How long does it take for the Blue Marble tree to start bearing fruit?",
      "options": "1-2yrs, 3-4yrs, 5-6yrs, 7-8months",
      "answer": "3-4yrs"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 79,
      "scientific_name": "Putranjiva roxburghii",
      "question": "Barks and leaves of Putranjiva roxburghii are medicinal",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 80,
      "scientific_name": "Putranjiva roxburghii",
      "question": "leaves and fruits of leaves of Putranjiva roxburghii are used as medicine for rheumatism",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 81,
      "scientific_name": "Kigelia Africana",
      "question": "The dried fruit of Kigelia Africana is used to make an alcoholic drink",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 82,
      "scientific_name": "Kigelia Africana",
      "question": "The planting site of Kigelia Africana should be chosen carefully because",
      "options": "The CO2 release can be harmful, Its falling fruit is dangerous",
      "answer": "Its falling fruit is dangerous"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 83,
      "scientific_name": "Weeping fig",
      "question": "The weeping fig is toxic for humans and animals",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 84,
      "scientific_name": "Weeping fig",
      "question": "Weeping figs trunks are sometimes braided for decorative appeal",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 85,
      "scientific_name": "Frangipani",
      "question": "The name Frangipani comes from the noble Frangipani family of which country?",
      "options": "France, Italy, Portugal, Greece",
      "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 86,
      "scientific_name": "Frangipani",
      "question": "The flower of Frangipani is the natural flower of which country?",
      "options": "Laos, Sudan, Nigeria, Egypt",
      "answer": "Laos"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 87,
      "scientific_name": "West Indian Mahogany",
      "question": "West Indian Mahogany is the national tree of which country?",
      "options": "Colombia, Aruba, Dominican republic, Venezuela",
      "answer": "Dominican republic"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 88,
      "scientific_name": "West Indian Mahogany",
      "question": "What was the West Indian Mahoganys first major use in England and Spain?",
      "options": "Furniture making, Ship making, Making Buildings",
      "answer": "Ship making"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 89,
      "scientific_name": "Tamarind",
      "question": "Tamarinds fruit is",
      "options": "Bitter, Salty, Tangy",
      "answer": "Tangy"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 90,
      "scientific_name": "Tamarind",
      "question": "The leaves and bark of Tamarin tree is edible",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 91,
      "scientific_name": "Stereospermum colais",
      "question": "Which part of Stereospermum colais is medicinal",
      "options": "root, leaves, bark",
      "answer": "root"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 92,
      "scientific_name": "Stereospermum colais",
      "question": "Parts of Stereospermum colais can help asthma patients",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "Stereospermum colais"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 93,
      "scientific_name": "Belliric Myrobalan",
      "question": "The fruit of Belliric Myrobalan is used as tanning leather",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 94,
      "scientific_name": "Belliric Myrobalan",
      "question": "Belliric Myrobalan has its uses in Ayurveda ",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 97,
      "scientific_name": "Roystonea regia",
      "question": "Roystonea regia is the national tree of?",
      "options": "Cuba, Colombia, Venezuela, Uruguay",
      "answer": "Cuba"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 98,
      "scientific_name": "Roystonea regia",
      "question": "Roystonea regia has religious role in which?",
      "options": "Hinduism, Christianity, Islam, Buddhism",
      "answer": "Christianity"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 101,
      "scientific_name": "Bamboo",
      "question": "Bamboo is famously the favourite food for which animal?",
      "options": "Panda, Tiger, Giraffe, Elephant",
      "answer": "Panda"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 102,
      "scientific_name": "Bamboo",
      "question": "Bamboo is the second fastest growing land plant",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 103,
      "scientific_name": "Purple orchild tree",
      "question": "The leaves and flowers of Purple orchild tree are edible",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 104,
      "scientific_name": "Purple orchild tree",
      "question": "The flowers of Purple orchild tree can be used in pickles",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 105,
      "scientific_name": "Tabebuia rosea",
      "question": "Tabebuia rosea is the national tree of",
      "options": "Honduras, Guatemala, El Salvador",
      "answer": "El Salvador"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 106,
      "scientific_name": "Tabebuia rosea",
      "question": "Tabebuia roseas can be used in Malaria treatment",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 107,
      "scientific_name": "Silver Oak",
      "question": "Wood from Silver Oak is used in which instrument",
      "options": "Ukulele, Guitar, Drum",
      "answer": "Guitar"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 108,
      "scientific_name": "Silver Oak",
      "question": "Silver Oaks is harmful as it contains Hydrogen Cyanide",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 109,
      "scientific_name": "Diploknema butyracea",
      "question": "Fat extracted from Diploknema butyraceas seeds is used in cooking",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 110,
      "scientific_name": "Diploknema butyracea",
      "question": "Diploknema butyracea has significant cultural associations in Nepal",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 111,
      "scientific_name": "Haldu",
      "question": "What part of Haldu acts as antiseptic?",
      "options": "Leaves, fruit, flowers, Bark",
      "answer": "Bark"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 112,
      "scientific_name": "Haldu",
      "question": "Haldu flowers in",
      "options": "June-August, September-November, April-June,March-May",
      "answer": "June-August"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 113,
      "scientific_name": "Cannon-ball tree",
      "question": "Cannon-ball tree is used in which temples",
      "options": "Hindu, Buddhist",
      "answer": "Hindu"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 114,
      "scientific_name": "Cannon-ball tree",
      "question": "Cannon-ball tree are called so because the flowers are spherical",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 115,
      "scientific_name": "Flame of the forest",
      "question": "Flame of the forest is called so because of its bright red fruit",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 116,
      "scientific_name": "Flame of the forest",
      "question": "Flowers of Flame of the forest were used to make colors for which festival?",
      "options": "Diwali, Dusshera, Pongal, Holi",
      "answer": "Holi"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 117,
      "scientific_name": "Peacock chaste tree",
      "question": "Peacock chaste tree flowers in ",
      "options": "April-May, June-July, August-September",
      "answer": "April-May"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 118,
      "scientific_name": "Peacock chaste tree",
      "question": "Bark is a useful part of Peacock chaste tree",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 119,
      "scientific_name": "Indian Tupil tree",
      "question": "Indian Tupil trees wood is used in the making of which instrument?",
      "options": "Hourglass drum, Guitar, Maracas, Drum sticks",
      "answer": "Hourglass drum"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 120,
      "scientific_name": "Indian Tupil tree",
      "question": "Flower of Indian Tupil tree played a part in which countrys independence movement?",
      "options": "Singapore, Malaysia, Sri Lanka, Indonesia",
      "answer": "Sri Lanka"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 121,
      "scientific_name": "Terminalia arjuna",
      "question": "In ancient times, Terminalia arjuna was used in treating",
      "options": "Lungs, Kidneys, Heart, Liver",
      "answer": "Liver"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 122,
      "scientific_name": "Terminalia arjuna",
      "question": "Terminalia arjuna is a common avenue tree",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 123,
      "scientific_name": "Sausage tree",
      "question": "The dried fruit of Sausage tree is used to make an alcoholic drink",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 124,
      "scientific_name": "Sausage tree",
      "question": "The planting site of Sausage tree should be chosen carefully because",
      "options": "The CO2 release can be harmful, Its falling fruit is dangerous",
      "answer": "Its falling fruit is dangerous"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 125,
      "scientific_name": "Gmelina arborea",
      "question": "The royal thrones from which country are carved from Gmelina arborea",
      "options": "Thailand, Japan, Myanmar, Indonesia",
      "answer": "Myanmar"
    },
    {
      "quiz_id": 126,
      "scientific_name": "Gmelina arborea",
      "question": "Gmelina arboreas leaves have medicinal properties",
      "options": "True, False",
      "answer": "False"
    }
  ]